

Applicant for:

Web Backend Developer (Java) ~\$1800

Dr.JOY 2 June 2020

Tạ Văn Tuấn

☑ tuantv.92@gmail.com

Main interests: Java, PHP

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Tạ Văn Tuấn skipped the cover letter.



Ta Van Tuan

Date of birth: August 25, 1992

Gender: Male

Phone: +84345911105

Email: tuantv.92@gmail.com

Address: Hanoi, Vietnam

OBJECTIVE

Software engineer with a passion for readable. I have a strong interest in Back-end with 5+ years of java experience, primarily working with highly scalable distributed systems built around microservices, various messaging and data storage technologies. I would like to become a software architect of a system with billions of users.

EDUCATION

May 2010 - Oct 2015

Ha Noi University Of Science And Technology (HUST)

Major: Software Engineering Grade: Good (GPA: 2.85)

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2018 - Present

Gear Inc

Senior server engineer

- · Known as Sixth Gear Studios
- Worked with: .NET Core, Redis, Jira, Spinnaker, DynamoDB,

ElasticSearch, MySQL, SQS.

Nov 2016 - April 2018

Neon Corporation

TechLead

- TechLead of some in-house projects, handle 30 million transactions per day, 6000 CCU at peak.
- Make strategies to migrate system from monolithic to microservice. Improve and handle the problems of the old system as: overload, data sync is wrong...
- Assist members in planning and implementing strategies to develop game logic.
- · Suggest training seminars and techniques
- Worked with: Java, Netty, Jetty, MySql, MongoDB, ElasticSearch, Hazelcast, Cassandra, Kafka, RabbitMQ.

Mar 2015 - Oct 2016

TapStudio

Backend Developer

- Learned and worked with ElectroServer and SmartFoxServer for building turnbased games.
- TapStutio where I contributed as senior software engineer on a microservice system written in Java. Helped create a full data processing pipeline with Cassandra, MySql, MongoDB, ElasticSeach, Redis, Hazelcast, RabbitMq and Kafka.

- Research Netty and Jetty framework to develop microservice system such as:
 - Assets management
 - Tracking logs
 - Centralized game configuration management
 - User management
 - Payment gateway

Services can deploy as standalone or cluster.

- · Worked with the Git, Ant, Maven, Jira
- My knowledge of the distributed and high performance system is improved a lot in TapStudio.

Jan 2013 - Feb 2015

Mimas coporation

TeamLeader

- Learned and worked with C# .Net, MS SQL, Phonegap, IIS, and Windows Platform in an enterprise environment using tools like Bitbucket and TFS team foundation server.
- Track the progress of weekly, monthly, quarterly and annual objectives Monitor and maintain store inventory
- Analyze consumer behavior and adjust product positioning
- Supervise and motivate staff to perform their best
- Make sure all employees adhere to company's policies and guidelines
- Develop applications, with some applications have millions of downloads, in which my outstanding application is Acolart has > 2M of downloads. The app allows you to create interesting collages from your photos, add effects or stickers to them, and share them with your friends, featured on many newspaper pages:
- http://www.windowscentral.com/acolart-windows-phone-photo-application

SKILLS

Programing Language	Java (5+ years) C# (2+ years)
Framework	Netty, Jetty, SmartFoxServer, ElectroServer, IIS
Server Operating System	Linux (+5 years) Windows (1+ years)
Database	MS SQL, MySQL, ElasticSearch, MongoDB, Cassandra
Cache	Redis, Hazelcast
Message queue	RabbitMQ, Kafka

INTERESTS

I like running, reading.